Guide to the Washington State University Capital Planning Building Files 1957-1998
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Capital Planning Building Files
1957-1998
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 273
Washington State University. Capital Planning
31.5 Linear feet of shelf space 32 Boxes
The collection consists of reports, plans, designs, and schematics relating to a large number of WSU Buildings; though a few earlier materials are included, the majority of the materials dates from the late 1980s to early 1990s.
A University Architect served as the construction officer at Washington State University from 1911 forward. The modern form of the office dates from 1947 when it became a full-time, staffed administrative department. In 1967 the University Architect office was renamed as Facilities Planning, and then to Facilities Development in 1993. In 2001 it was renamed as Capital Planning. While Capital Planning is responsible for major planning and development, smaller projects are conducted by Facilities Operations. Facilities Operations descended from the Physical Plant in 1998, which in turn descended from Building and Grounds in 1967. While each line of programs has existed separately, some migration in function has occurred over the years. The primary difference between Capital Planning and Facilities Operations is the cost of the project in question - initially items costing less than $1,000,000 were assigned to Fac Ops, and those costing more to CP. By 2009, this break point is between $1,500,000 and $2,000,000.
Many terms historically used to describe individuals and communities with disabilities are offensive and were used to dismiss, discount and dehumanize these individuals and communities. Terms often focused on a perceived impairment and not the person. MASC recognizes the harm caused by these terms. We retain the language in this finding aid to document history and preserve context.
The collection consists of reports, plans, designs, and schematics relating to a large number of WSU Buildings; though a few earlier materials are included, the majority of the materials dates from the late 1980s to early 1990s.
The collection is maintained in the order in which it was received in the Archives from Capital Planning, and loosely consists of two series in a close-to-alphabetical order.
The majority of this collection is open and available for research use. A few files are marked as confidential or classified (these are primarily identified as Attorney General files or Issues and Claims files; please contact Capital Planning if you wish access to these) and access to those may be restricted. These files are labeled in this page as RESTRICTED, each box containing restricted material is so labeled, and individual restricted folders are stickered as such.
These records were transfered to Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections from Capital Planning on February 10, 2004 (UA 2004-01).
The WSU Archives hold a number of other Capital Plannng collections; to locate these please view our Archives' Collections List and our Accessions List, looking for the various names under which this department has operated: University Architect, Facilities Planning, Facilities Development, Capital Planning.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Capital Planning -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University. Capital Planning and Development -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Development -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Planning -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University -- Buildings -- History -- Archives; >Washington State University. Capital Planning; Washington State University. Capital Planning and Development; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Development; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Planning
College buildings -- Washington (State)
Architecture; Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- College of Agriculture. Controlled Environment Laboratories and Growth Chambers. 1/1976. (Box 1)
- Agriculture Sciences Building - Program Statement. Clark and Hulbert Halls. 11/1965. (Box 1)
- Agriculture Sciences Building - Clark Hall Preliminary Design. 7/1968. / Lloyd J. Lovegren and Associates Architects (Box 1)
- Agriculture Sciences Building - Preliminary Design. 11/1969. / Lloyd J. Lovegren and Associates Architects (Box 1)
- Animal Disease Biotechnology Facility Value Engineering Design Development.12/1992. / KIM and Associates, Ltd. (Box 1)
- Animal Disease Biotechnology (ADBF) Facility Site Selection Study. 6/1991. / Burke Lee Architects, Planners and Landscape Architects (Box 1)
- ADBF - Design Development. 12/1992. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 1)
- ADBF - Schematic Design Brochure. 6/1992. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 1)
- ADBF - Program Statement. 1/1992. (Box 1)
- ADBF Partial Specifications (Third Submittal). 12/1992. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 1)
- ADBF - Construction Document Phase/Structural Calculation. Vol. I Final Submittal. 2/1994. / Structural Design Northwest, Inc.; Garrick A. Dung - Professional Engineer (Box 1)
- ADBF - Construction Document Phase/Structural Calculation. Vol. II - Final Submittal. 2/1994. / Structural Design Northwest, Inc.; Garrick A. Dung - Professional Engineer (Box 1)
- ADBF - Construction Document Phase/Structural Calculation. Vol. III - Final Submittal. 2/1994. / Structural Design Northwest. Inc.; Garrick A. Dung - Professional Engineer (Box 1)
- ADBF - Architectural Specifications - Volume I of 2. 2/1992. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 1)
- ADBF - Mechanical and Electrical Specification - Volume II of II. 3/1994. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 1)
- Alumni Center - Schematic Design Brochure. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 2)
- Alumni Center - Interior Design. 4/1988. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 2)
- Alumni Center - Furnishings Presentations. 7/1988. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 2)
- Alumni Center - Specifications. 12/1987. / Northwest Architectural Company (Box 2)
- Athletic Facilities Study - ALSC Architects. 6/1996. / ALSC Architects, P.S. (Box 2)
- Animal Sciences Laboratory Building (ASLB) - Schematic Design Submittal. / MBT Associates (Box 2)
- ASLB Building - Schematic Design Submittal. / MBT Associates (Box 2)
- ASLB - Project Manual, Vol. I. Sec 0 - 14. 9/1995. / MBT Architecture (Box 2)
- ASLB - Project Manual, Vol. II. Sec 15 - 16. 9/1995. / MBT Architecture (Box 2)
- ASLB - Design Development Value Engineering. 11/1994. / Ehninger Fetzer Tholen (Box 2)
- ASLB - ***Revised*** Construction Documents Estimate. 8/1995. / Ackroyd Cost Control Consultants (Box 2)
- ASLB - Energy Conservation Report/Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 2/1995. / Affiliated Engineers NW, Inc. (Box 2)
- ASLB - Schematic Design Estimate (Final). 4/1994. / Ackroyd Cost Control Consultants (Box 2)
- ASLB - Addendum NO. 1. 9/1995. / MBT Architecture (Box 2)
- ASLB - Addendum NO. 2. 9/1995. / MBT Architecture (Box 2)
- ASLB - Addendum NO. 4. 10/1995. / MBT Architecture (Box 2)
- ASLB - Addendum NO. 5. 10/1995. / MBT Architecture (Box 2)
- Completion Of Laboratory - Central Animal Laboratory Facility. 5/1975. / Barnard and Holloway, Architects (Box 2)
- Veterinary Animal Holding and Quarantine Facilities Isolation Building Specification. 11/1979. / Architects: Barnard and Holloway; Mechanical: Rice and LunhElectrical: Stingle - Atwood (Box 2)
- Completion of Large Animal Isolation Facility - Specifications. 3/1982. / Barnard and Holloway (Box 2)
- The Architecture Interior Design Landscape Architecture Facility @ WSU Design Report. 5/1981. / Architects: Adkison Leigh Sims Cuppage (Box 2)
- Design Associates: Simmer Gunsul Frasca Partnership. / Landscape Architects: Jongejan Gerard McNeal (Box 2)
- A Study of Alternative Sites - Architecture, Interior Design, Landscape Architecture Facility. 3/1980. / Architects: Adkison Leigh Sims Cuppage; Design Associates: Simmer Gunsul Frasca PartnershipLandscape Architects: Jongejan Gerard McNeal (Box 2)
- Avery Hall - English Building Phase 1. 11/1970. / Architects: Fred Bassetti and Company; Mechanical Engineers: Valentine, Fisher and TomlinsonElectrical Engineers: Beverly A. Travis and Associates; Landscape Architects: Richard Haag Associates (Box 2)
- Multi Purpose Coliseum (Beasley) Program and Site Analysis. 12/1968. / John Graham and Company - Architects/Planners/Engineers (Box 3)
- Multi Purpose Coliseum Schematic Design. 4/1969. / John Graham and Company - Architects/Planners/Engineers (Box 3)
- Multi Purpose Coliseum - Preliminary Design. 10/1969. / John Graham and Company - Architects/Planners/Engineers (Box 3)
- Beasley Performing Arts Coliseum. Roof Structure Evaluation - Volume 1 Report. 5/1988. / Peden Petersen Lee, R. S. Consulting Engineers (Box 3)
- Beasley Performing Arts Coliseum. Roof Structure Evaluation - Volume 2 Calculations. 5/1988. / Peden Petersen Lee, R.S. Consulting Engineers (Box 3)
- Biosciences Building Phase II - Program. 11/1973. (Box 3)
- Biosciences Building Phase II - Preliminary Design (Kolb and Stansfield). 7/1974. (Box 3)
- Biosciences Building Phase II - Specifications (Kolb and Stansfield). 3/1975. (Box 3)
- Biological Sciences Building (Eastlick) - Preliminary Presentation. 11/1959. / Decker and Christenson AIA Architects (Box 3)
- Bohler Gymnasium Addition - Predesign Study. 10/1992. / Sasaki Associates, Inc.; Stewart Associates (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Addition - Schematic Design. 11/1994. / Architect: Sasaki Associates; Associated Architect: Stewart AssociatesStructural and Civil Engineers: Summit Technology; Mechanical Engineers: Notkin Engineering; Electrical Engineers: Elcon Associates (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Addition - 100% Design Development Submittal 1 of 2. 5/1995. / Architect: Sasaki Associates. Inc.; Mechanical Engineer: Notkin Engineering. Inc. (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Addition - 100% Design Development Submittal 2 of 2. 5/1995. / Architect: Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Addn. - Structural Calculations 1 of 2. 2/1996. / Prepared by Summit Technology (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Add. - Structural Calculations 2 of 2. 2/1996. / Prepared by Summit Technology (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Add. - Construction Bid Documents 1 of 2. 2/1996. / Sasaki Architects, Inc. (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Add. - 100% Design Mechanical Calculations. 5/1996. / Architect: Sasaki Associates, Inc.; Mechanical Engineer: Notkin Engineering In. (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Renovation - Schematic Design Value Engineering. 6/1996. / EFT Architects/Planners/Project Managers (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Renovation - Schematic Design. 6/1996. / Sasaki Architects (Box 3)
- Bohler Gym Add. - Load Calculations. 5/1996. / Elcon Associates. inc. (Box 3)
- Boiler No. 8 - Proposal for Engineering Services. 11/1975. / Bovay Engineers, Inc. (Box 3)
- Bryan Hall Remodel - Schematic Design Brochure. 7/1972. / James and Hicks, Architects; Rice and Luhn, Mechanical EngineersJoseph Dyole and Assoc. Electrical Engineers; Atwood - Hinzman, Structural Engineers (Box 3)
- Child and Family Studies Center - Building Program. 10/1967. (Box 4)
- Child Care Center - Bldg Assessments Report (Rogers Orton Dining Hall). 12/1991. / The Tsang Partnership, Inc. (Box 4)
- Child Care Center Building Program. 6/1991. / The Tsang Partnership, Inc. (Box 4)
- Child Care Facility - Design Development Phase. 7/1992. / The Tsang Partnership. Inc. (Box 4)
- Child Care Center - Schematic Design Phase Report. 1/1992. / The Tsang Partnership, Inc. (Box 4)
- Child Care Facility - Schematic Design. 4/1992. / The Tsang Partnership. Inc. (Box 4)
- Child Care Facility - Design Development Phase. 7/1992. (Box 4)
- Child Care Facility Project Manual. 2/1993. / Architect: The Tsang Partnership, Inc.; Structural Engineer: Chulker, Putnam Collins and Scott, Inc.Mechanical Engineer: Thomas J. Gerard and Assoc.; Electrical Engineers. Doyle Engineering, Inc. (Box 4)
- Child Care Center Playground. Report of Subsurface Exploration and Geotechnical Studies. 4/1994. / Gifford Consultants. inc. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Project Manual General Volume I of III. 6/1987. / Architect: Brooks Hensley Creager Architects P.S.; Landscape Architect: Hellstorm AssociatesElectrical Engineers: Doyle Engineering Inc.; Vibration Consultants: Applied Dynamics Inc. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Project Manual. Mechanical Specifications Volume II of III. 6/1987. / Architect: Brooks Hensley Creager Architects P.S. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Project Manual. Electrical Specification Volume III of III. 6/1987. / Architect: Brooks Hensley Creager Architects P.S. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Index/ Sec. 16000 - 16851. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Section 15010 - General Provisions. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Engineering Calculations. / Brooks Hensley Creager Architects, P.S. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Schematic Design Documents. 11/1984. / Brooks Hensley Creager Architects, P.S. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Schematic Design Documents. 9/1986. / Brooks Hensley Creager Architects, P.S. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Pedestrian Corridor Design Development of College Avenue From Library Road to Stadium Way. / Brooks Hensley Creager Architects P.S. (Box 4)
- Chemistry Building - Site Study Selection. 3/1984. / Burke/Lee A joint venture (Box 4)
- Specifications for a Crew Shellhouse. 2/8/1984. (Box 5)
- Fulmer Hall: Chemical Waste Collection Site Facility. 6/24/1994. (Box 5)
- Schematic Design Brochure: Chemical Waste Collection Sites - Vet Complex. 9/3/1996. (Box 5)
- Schematic Design Brochure: Chemical Waste Collection Sites - Eastlick Hall, Wegner Hall, Engineering Complex and Silver Recovery Units. 11/18/1994. (Box 5)
- Creamery Annex: Schematic Design Brochure. 11/10/1998. (Box 5)
- Chemical Sciences Bld: Site Selection Study. 11/1980. (Box 5)
- Chemistry Building: Program Statement. 3/1984. (Box 5)
- Chemistry Building #3 Section 15010 - General Provisions. (Box 5)
- Site Study: Cancer Research and Training Center. 11/1976. (Box 5)
- Building Program, Preliminary Draft: Cancer Research and Training Center. 11/1976. (Box 5)
- Proposal: Carpenter Hall Renewal. 5/1984. (Box 5)
- Carpenter Hall Schematic Design. 4/24/1987. (Box 5)
- Carpenter Hall Design Development. 10/16/1987. (Box 5)
- Carpenter Hall Renewal Addendums.. (Box 5)
- Centeral Chilled Water System. 1973 - 1974. (Box 5)
- Centeral Water Chilling and Dist. A Feasibility Study. 1973 - 1974. (Box 5)
- Centeral Campus Storm Sewer and Circulation Improvements Study. 4/1984. (Box 5)
- Cleveland Hall. 10/1961. (Box 5)
- Cleveland Hall, Addition to. (Box 5)
- Department of Anthropology. (Box 5)
- College Hall Renovation: Design Development. 1/1982. (Box 5)
- College Hall. (Box 5)
- Project Manual: College Hall Renovation. 8/12/1982. (Box 5)
- Comp. Sci. Bld. Martin Academic/Stadium. 7/1971. (Box 5)
- Computer Sciences - Mathmatics Building, Phase 1, Martin Stadium/Academic Center Phase II. 10/22/1976. (Box 5)
- Schematic Design: Martin Stadium Academic Center Phase II Computer Science Building. 3/15/1975. (Box 5)
- Computer Sciences - Mathmatics Building, Phase 1, Martin Stadium/Academic Center Phase II. 5/1976. (Box 5)
- Open Plan Feasibility Study: Computer Sciences/Mathmatics Building. 4/1980. (Box 5)
- Cancer Research: Preliminary Concepts (along side of box). 12/1976. (Box 5)
- Campus Downtown Pedestrian Corridor. (Box 6)
- West Entrance Pedestrian Way - Specifications. 7/1986. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture Architects/Landscape Architects (Box 6)
- Compton Union (Wilson) - Expansion Program Statement. (Box 6)
- Compton Union Building - Technical Report. Graphical Results from a Telephone Survey of WSU Student. Faculty, and Staff on the Compton Union Building (CUB) and Campus Recreation Facilities. 9/1996. (Box 6)
- SESRC (Social and Economic Sciences Research Center) Report # 96 - 22 (CUB6 # 1265). (Box 6)
- Comparative Behavior Laboratory - Schematic Design Brochure Addition to. 1/1966. / Victor Louis Wulff Architect. AIA and Associates (Box 6)
- Colorado Street preliminary Design - Technical Memorandum. 10/1994. / CH2M Hill Engineers Planners Economists Scientists (Box 6)
- Commons Remodeling Program for Ground Floor. Listings of Projected Uses and Requirements. 5/1971. (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Master Plan. 11/1988. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Schematic Design Submittal. 1/1989. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facilities - Proposed Phase 1 Additions. Subsurface Exploration and Geotechnical Engineering Report. 1/1989. / RittenHouse-Zeman and Associates/Geotechnical and Hydrogeological Experts (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Buckley Cost Estimate. 2/1989. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Volume 1 - Specifications. 11/1989. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Volume 2 - Architectural Details. 11/1989. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Project Manual Volume 1 Specifications. 4/1990. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Cost Estimate and Area Comparison Charts. Schematic Design Phase. 4/1992. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Schematic Design Submittal The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA. 4/1992. (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Design Development Submittal (Buckley WA): Design Description, Cost Estimate, Area Comparison, Proposed Time Schedule. 9/1992. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Outline Specifications (Buckley WA). 9/1992. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Project Manual Volume 1 Specifications. 4/1993. / The BJSS Group Architecture and Planners AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Project Manual Volume 2 Details and Schedule. 4/1993. / The BJSS Group Architects and Planners, AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Project Manual Volume 1 Specifications. 10/1993. / The BJSS Group Architects and Planners, AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II Project Manual Volume 2 Details and Schedule. 10/1993. / The BJSS Group Architects and Planners, AIA (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Phase II - Structural Calculations. 1/1993. / AKB Consulting Engineers/BJSS (Box 6)
- Dairy Forage Facility - Western Washington Research and Extension Center (Puyallup) Veterinary Research - Diagnostic Center. 8/1987. / Gross, Thurman and DeMers, Joe, P.S. (Box 6)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Building. 11/1982 - Revised 12/1983. / The Callison Partnership, Ltd. (Box 7)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Bldg. Site Selection Study. 8/1982. / Burke/Lee A Joint Venture (Box 7)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Bldg. Design Development. 7/1983. (Box 7)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Bldg. - Building Program (Original). 12/1983. (Box 7)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Bldg. - (Revised). 12/1983. (Box 7)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Bldg. - Specifications Cummings Schiatter Associates. 4/1984. / Loschky Marquardt and Nesholm (Box 7)
- Engineering Teaching Research Laboratory Building (ETRL). Project Manual Volume 1. 3/1996. / Callison Architecture. Inc. (Box 7)
- ETRL Building - Project Manual Volume 2. 3/1996. / Callison Architecture, Inc. (Box 7)
- ETRL - Project Manual Volume I - (Placed On Top in Box). 5/1995. / Callison Architecture, Inc. (Box 7)
- ETRL Building - Electrical Panel Schedule. 5/1995. / Callison Architecture, Inc. (Box 7)
- ETRL Building Schematic Design Submittal - Scheme T. / Callison Architecture, Inc. (Box 7)
- ETRL Building - Design Development outline Specifications. 7/1994. / Callison Architecture (Box 7)
- ETRL Building - Addendum #1 and Addendum #2. 3/1996. / Callison Architecture (Box 7)
- ETRL Building - Project Manual - Volume I Bid Set. 3/1996. / Callison Architecture, Inc. (Box 7)
- Electrical/Mechanical Engineering Bldg. - Addendums No. 2 and 3. 1984. / The Callison Partnership, Ltd. - Predesign Consultant (Box 7)
- Engineering Teaching Research Laboratory Building. Energy Conservation Report - Life Cycle Cost Analysis. 7/1994. / Riley Engineering, Inc.; The Callison Partnership Ltd. (Box 8)
- English Building - Phase 1 - Avery Hall. / Architects: Fred Bassetti and Company; Mechanical Engineers: Valentine, Fisher and TomlinsonElectrical Engineers: Beverly A. Travis and Associates; Landscape Architects: Richard Haag Associates (Box 8)
- Experimental Animal Laboratory - Program. 6/1975. (Box 8)
- Experimental Animal Laboratory - Waste Treatment Facilities - Engineering Report. / Parametrix, Inc. (Box 8)
- Experimental Animal Laboratory - Design Development. 10/1975. / Architects: Kirk, Wallace, McKinley, AIA and Associates;Structural Engineers: Skilling, Helle, Christiansen, RobertsonMechanical and Electrical: Valentine, Fisher and Tomlinson; Electrical: Sparli (Box 8)
- Experimental Animal Laboratory - Draft Impact Statement. 12/1976. / Parametrix, Inc. (Box 8)
- Facility Condition Survey - McAllister/ Kruegel Resident Halls CO 11063. / SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 8)
- Facility Condition Survey - Administration Annex CO 10153. 7/1990. / SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 8)
- Facility Condition Survey - Van Doren Hall CO 10153. 7/1990. / SCM Consultants. Inc. (Box 8)
- Facility Condition Survey - Chemical Engineering Building CO 10153. 7/1990. / SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 8)
- Facility Condition Survey - Commons Building CO 10153. 7/1990. / SCM Consultants, Inc. (Box 8)
- Family Student Housing Environmental Checklist. 5/1994. / Burke/Lee Architects/Landscape Architects/Planners (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall Remodeling - Phase II. 5/1980. (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall/Annex Renewal - Value Engineering Study. 8/1993. / Meng Associates (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall and Annex - Fume Hood Survey - Draft. 11/1993. / Mclellen and Copenhagan; Mahium and Nordfors, McKinley, Gordon (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall/Annex Renewal - Schematic Design Submittal. / McKinley Gordon PSC, Architect - McKinley Gordon PSC; Ratti Swenson Perbix, Inc. - Structural Engineer.H.K. Kim Engineers, Inc. - MBE Structural Engineer.; Riley Engineering - Mechanical and Electr (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall Remodeling - Building Program Statement - Phase II. (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall - Fulmer Hall Annex Renewal - Construction Documents. Project Manual Volume 1. Specification 0 - 4. 4/1995. / Mahlum and Nordfors McKinley Gordon (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall Remodeling - Building Program Statement. Phases II and III. 8/1979. (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall Phases I and II Completion - Specifications. 12/1983. / Waldron Pomeroy Smith Foote and Akira Architects (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall Remodeling - Program Statement. 11/1992. (Box 8)
- Fulmer Hall/Fulmer Annex - Program Statement. 5/1993. (Box 8)
- Fine Arts Building Program - Building Program - Design Disciplines Building Phase II (worn brown unbound notebook). / Prepared as a collaborative effort by the Departments of Architecture, Fine Arts, Interior Design and Landscape Architecture (Box 8)
- Fine Arts Center Mechanical Systems Renovations - Specifications. / Halvorson, Beach and Bower Inc.; Waldron Pomeroy Smith Foote and Akira ArchitectsRobert Fossatti Associates (Box 8)